<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Aswan Tourism</string>
    <string name="image_of_the_place">image of the place</string>
    <string name="directions">Directions</string>
    <string name="abusimble">Abu Simbel, site of two temples built by the Egyptian king Ramses II (reigned 1279–13 BCE), now located in Aswan governorate, southern Egypt. In ancient times the area was at the southern frontier of pharaonic Egypt, facing Nubia. The four colossal statues of Ramses in front of the main temple are spectacular examples of ancient Egyptian art. </string>
    <string name="komombo">One of the most unusual temples of Ancient Egypt, Kom Ombo was mainly built during the Ptolemaic Dynasty from 180 - 47 BCE, although there is evidence that it is stood upon an earlier temple.

        The temple is unique for its dedication to two different deities: the local crocodile-headed god Sobek, and the first "god of the Kingdom", the falcon-headed god Horus the Elder (also called Haroeris). This double dedication was deliberate. Not only is it architecturally duplicated, with two sets of courts, hypostyle halls and sanctuaries, the twin temple is symbolic of the local and universalist themes that the two different deities represented.</string>
    <string name="philae">The monuments of Philae include many structures dating predominantly to the Ptolemaic Period (332–30 BC). The most prominent of these is a temple begun by Ptolemy II Philadelphus (285–246 BC), which he dedicated to Isis, the mother of Horus, the god of kingship. A scene in the mammisi, or birth room, where the birth of Horus was celebrated, depicts Isis suckling her son Horus in the marshes.</string>
    <string name="edfu">Edfu Temple is one of the most striking and complete of ancient Egyptian temples and is dedicated to the worship of the god Horus. Situated on the western bank of the Nile, its construction began during the reign of Ptolemy III (246–221 BC) in 237 BC, but was completed in the reign of Ptolemy XII (80–51 BC) in 57 BC, 180 years later.

        The temple remained buried under layers of settlement debris for millennia, which is why its architectural and decorative elements have survived so well. In 1860 the French archaeologist Auguste Mariette uncovered and restored parts of the temple.</string>
    <string name="nubian">The Nubia Museum harbors the history of the "Land of Gold" as the word Nubia in the Hieroglyphic, language of ancient Egypt in which pictorial symbols are used to represent meaning and sounds, means the "Land of Gold"…Hence, this land, over times, was abounding in monumental treasures.

    The Nubia Museum, in Aswan, as a matter of fact, is deemed to be one of the most important Egyptian museums. A number of factors have combined together, yielding the magnificence of such museum, as it is the only unique open museum of its kind.</string>
    <string name="agakhan">"At first sight, the Mausoleum of the Agha Khan in Aswan may appear to you as an austere and isolated building, on the west bank of the Nile River. Inspired by the architecture of the Cairo Fatimids, the structure is recognizable by its elegance and by its special use of pink granite. It was built at the request of the begum, wife of the Aga Khan III who died in 1957.The begum who died in 2000 lived in the white villa below but closed the mausoleum to the public in 1997 to allow the deceased to rest in peace away from the bustle of the living. Nevertheless, the spot is more than worth a visit, be it for the serenity of the place or the amazing panoramas of the Nile and the villa below."</string>
    <string name="ferial">Very pleasant spot right in the middle of the city, which stands on the high rocky east bank of the Nile near the Cataract hotel, with fantastic views along the Nile river in both directions. Very good place to take spectacular pictures of the sunset over the western mountains when in Aswan, views are nearly equally great as from the Cataract hotel proper. It is not many visitors in the park in the evenings during the sunset time. Entrance ticket costs just 1 or 2 EGP.</string>
    <string name="gharb">Located on the banks of the Nile near Aswan, the colourful village of Gharb Seheyl gives a feeling of travelling back in time to ancient Nubia, the home to one of Africa\'s oldest civilisations. Today, the village of Gharb Soheyl has become a popular destination for those wanting a peaceful escape the hustle and bustle of the big Egyptian cities, and for those wanting a taste of ancient life in Nubia. It is home to colourful Nubian houses, a golden beach where it\'s perfectly safe to swim, and a souk selling traditional local handicrafts, foods and spices.</string>

</resources>